privitize.com 2014-06-16

# Privitize VPN - Privacy Policy

**Privitize VPN**

**Privacy Policy**

**Last Modified: October 19th, 2012**

This document describes what information is collected by us from any user of the Privitize VPN (collectively or individually "User(s)"), as well as our use and disclosure of that information.

**NOTE TO KIDS:**  PRIVITIZE VPN IS NOT AVAILABLE TO PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF 18. 

_If you are under 18 years of age, please do not use Privitize VPN._

**Our Commitment to User Privacy:**

Privitize does not collect any personally identifiable information on Privitize VPN. Privitize VPN automatically collects certain non-personally identifiable information from Users that is used in the aggregate only. Privitize does not collect, store, or share any permanent identifiers of Users, including IP addresses. Please note that Privitize VPN only enables privacy and encrypts user Internet sessions when it is turned ON. Having Privitize VPN on the desktop, without turning it ON does not do anything. Unless Users turn Privitize VPN ON and opt into the service, Privitize VPN will be completely idle.

**Our Commitment to Web Security:**

Privitize VPN encrypts every page visited by our Users, thus protecting communications between each User and the Internet. Privitize Privitize VPN employs certain physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of any information collected. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant that the safeguards will be uninterrupted or effective, or that any information you transmit to Privitize VPN will remain secure, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Privitize employs certain techniques and technologies to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. If Privitize learns of a security systems breach, we may post a notice on the Privitize website to notify Users. Please note that Privitize VPN helps secure your Internet session, not your computer. Privitize VPN does not protect your computer from viruses or malware. We recommend getting anti-virus/anti-malware solutions from one of our reputable partners in order to also help secure your computer.

**The Information Privitize VPN Collects:**

**"Automatically Collected" Information.**  When you use the Privitize VPN, some information may be automatically recorded using different types of proprietary technology. The automatically-collected information does not identify a User personally, and Privitize only uses the automatically collected information for various purposes, including but not limited to monitoring of the traffic statistics, VPN usage by time, internet speed and so on.

**The Way Privitize Uses Information Collected from Privitize VPN:**

Privitize may use automatically-collected information in the aggregate to monitor the advertisements displayed on the Privitize VPN, and for purposes of research or analysis. Please note that by having Privitize VPN on your computer, but not turned on, no information is collected by Privitize. Anonymous web information may only be collected when you turn Privitize VPN ON.

**When Privitize Discloses Information Collected from Privitize VPN:**

Privitize may share anonymous data with a variety of third parties, including its affiliates, advertisers, and other current and prospective business partners. Privitize may use anonymous data collected for website administration, advertising, and promotional purposes, and may share such information with various affiliated and unaffiliated entities for such purposes.  
Privitize may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess technology that allows Privitize to customize the advertising and marketing messages Users receive while using the Privitize VPN, and those outside companies may have access to anonymous data that was collected from Privitize VPN users.  
Privitize may disclose automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist such parties in understanding the usage, viewing, and demographic patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Privitize VPN.

**Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites on the Privitize VPN:**

Privitize allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within Privitize VPN. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links. Any third parties including advertisers may automatically receive the virtual IP Address assigned by Privitize. Your original IP address will not be collected or provided to any third parties by Privitize. Advertisers may also use other technologies (such as cookies, javascript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. Privitize's Privitize VPN Privacy Notice does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or other web sites visited by Users. Please note that this Privacy Notice will not apply to your activities or any information you disclose while using any third-party products or services or otherwise interacting with third parties. How third parties handle and use your personal information related to their sites and services is governed by their security, privacy and other policies, if any, and not this Privacy Notice. Privitize has no responsibility for any third party's policies, or any third party's compliance with them. Anyone may opt out of the cookies as directed by NAI opt-out page, which is currently located at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**Changes and Updates to this Privitize VPN Privacy Notice:**

This Privitize VPN Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "last modified" notice above. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Privitize VPN constitutes your agreement to this Privitize VPN Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

**Privitize Contact Information:**

Please contact Privitize with any questions or comments about this Privitize VPN Privacy Notice at info@privitize.com. Please note that if you contact Privitize, you will be disclosing your personal information, and the use of such personal information will be governed by the Privitize Privacy Policy.
